<?xml version="1.0"?>
<russellgigs>
<!--addnode-->
<gig>
	<nodecreation>03/15/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>Wednesday March 31, 2010 :: 1:30-2:15</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at the National Cherry Blossom Festival at the Target Cultural Performance Stage at Sylvan Theater on the grounds of the Washington Monument (Corner of 15th St. &amp;amp; Independence Ave. SW), 1:30 pm to 2:15 pm </details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>05/20/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>May 28, 2010 :: 7:00 - 10:00</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at the Regency at Dominion Valley for a private engagement as part of the Regency's Jazz Under the Stars series.</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>08/20/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>August 27 &amp; 28, 2010 :: 8:00 - 12:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at McLoone's Pier House, 141 National Plaza National Harbor MD. 20745.</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>10/07/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>October 8 &amp; 9, 2010 :: 8:00 - 12:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at McLoone's Pier House, 141 National Plaza National Harbor MD. 20745.</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>10/27/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>November 26 &amp; 27, 2010 :: 8:00 - 12:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at McLoone's Pier House, 141 National Plaza National Harbor MD. 20745.</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>11/01/2010</nodecreation>
	<date>November 6, 2010 :: 2:00-4:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing at the Grand Opening of Zachary's Jewelry, located at 522 Ritchie Highway, Severna Park MD. 21146. Come join us for an afternoon of Jewelry and Jazz!</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>07/19/2011</nodecreation>
	<date>August 21, 2011 :: 7:00 - 9:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum will be appearing as a Duo this Thursday, August 21st from 7pm. - 9pm. at the Urban Eats Arts and Music Cafe, a new cafe just outside of DC located at 3311 Rhode Island Ave., Mount Rainier, MD 20712. When you stop in be sure to say hello!</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>04/19/2012</nodecreation>
	<date>April 20, 2012 :: 7:00pm &#x2013; 9:00pm</date>
	<details>The Russell Sledge Continuum has returned! Come join the quartet, with guest vocalist, for an evening of Jazz at the Agape Cafe, located at the St. Paul United Methodist Church, 6634 St. Barnabas Road Oxon Hill MD. 20745.</details>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>04/19/2012</nodecreation>
	<date>April 20, 2012 :: 7:00pm &#x2013; 9:00pm</date>
	<details/>
</gig>
<gig>
	<nodecreation>nodecreation here</nodecreation>
	<date>September 27, 2012 :: 6:00-9:00pm</date>
	<details>For the first time this year, the Russell Sledge Continuum will be at the beautiful 21st Amendment Bar &amp; Grill, located inside the Holiday Inn Capitol 550 C St. SW Washington DC 20024. If you\'re ready to enjoy the great food and atmosphere of the 21st Amendment Bar &amp; Grill, then we are ready to have you come join us and swing!</details>
</gig>
<gig><nodecreation>nodecreation here</nodecreation><date>October 25 2012 :: 6:00-9:00pm</date><details>
The Russell Sledge Continuum returns to the beautiful 21st Amendment Bar &amp; Grill, located inside the Holiday Inn Capitol 550 C St. SW Washington DC 20024. Come prepared to swing while you enjoy the great food and atmosphere, and be sure to stop by and say hello! 
</details></gig>
<gig><nodecreation>nodecreation here</nodecreation><date>November 8, 2012 :: 6:00-9:00pm</date><details>
The Russell Sledge Continuum returns to the 21st Amendment Bar &amp; Grill for what may be their final performance there this year. The swing will continue, so come and help us make this the best date yet!
</details></gig>
<gig><nodecreation>nodecreation here</nodecreation>
<date>February 21, 2013 :: 6:00-9:00pm</date><details>Continuing the music from last year, the Russell Sledge Continuum will be at the beautiful 21st Amendment Bar &amp; Grill For the first time in 2013! Located inside the Holiday Inn Capitol 550 C St. SW Washington DC 20024, you will enjoy great food and great music. We're looking forward to seeing you there!</details></gig></russellgigs>
